(Leonard:)You are unbelievable.
I don't know why I put up with you.
(Leonard:)- You're controlling, you're irritating...
- There you go again. Nag, nag, nag.
(Sheldon:)You're only proving my point, little lady.
You know what, screw you, Sheldon.
You're the most annoying person
I've ever met.
(Sheldon:)I'm annoying?
You criticize my behavior all the time.
"Sheldon, don't talk about
your bowel movements over breakfast."
"Sheldon, when the president
of the university...
(Sheldon:)...is giving a eulogy at a funeral,
don't yawn and point at your watch."
"Sheldon, don't throw away my shirts
because they're ugly."
(Sheldon:)You're impossible.
That's it, I don't have to put up with this.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I have your signature
on a roommate agreement that says you do.
Aww. Here's what I think
of your roommate agreement.
- You pick that up right now.
- No.
(Sheldon:)Roommate agreement,
section 27, paragraph 5:
"The roommate agreement, like the
American flag, cannot touch the ground."
(Leonard:)I don't care.
(Leonard:)I don't have to do anything you say, because
I don't think I wanna live here anymore.
- Where are you going?
- To live with Penny...
(Leonard:)...not you, you crazy bastard.
- Crazy bastard?
- Yes.
- Leonard, wait.
- What?
(Sheldon:)Dobby the Elf dies in book seven.